{
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "dog",
      "answer": "собака",
      "category": "animals",
      "createdAt": "2023-05-24",
      "isLearned": false
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "cat",
      "answer": "кіт",
      "category": "animals",
      "createdAt": "2023-05-24",
      "isLearned": true
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "parrot",
      "answer": "папуга",
      "category": "animals",
      "createdAt": "2023-05-24",
      "isLearned": true
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "orange",
      "answer": "апельсин",
      "category": "plants",
      "createdAt": "2023-05-25",
      "isLearned": false
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "banana",
      "answer": "банан",
      "category": "plants",
      "createdAt": "2023-05-26",
      "isLearned": true
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "kiwi",
      "answer": "ківі",
      "category": "plants",
      "createdAt": "2023-05-26",
      "isLearned": false
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "bear",
      "answer": "переносити",
      "category": "verbs",
      "createdAt": "2023-06-01",
      "isLearned": false
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "overcome",
      "answer": "подолати",
      "category": "verbs",
      "createdAt": "2023-06-01",
      "isLearned": false
    },
    {
      "id": 0.5887520439476455,
      "question": "onion",
      "answer": "цибуля",
      "category": "plants",
      "createdAt": "2023-06-05T20:15:27.603Z",
      "isLearned": false
    },
    {
      "id": 0.36733145044390714,
      "question": "fish",
      "answer": "риба",
      "category": "animals",
      "createdAt": "2023-06-05T20:16:38.925Z",
      "isLearned": false
    },
    {
      "id": 0.041333083180946195,
      "question": "bird",
      "answer": "птах",
      "category": "animals",
      "createdAt": "2023-06-06T09:09:04.550Z",
      "isLearned": false
    }
  ]
}
